tollfreeforwarding.com 2019-08-08

# Privacy Policy | TollFreeForwarding.com

The policies below are applicable to IFN.com Inc. d/b/a TollFreeForwarding.com and other sites and systems on the Internet owned and operated by IFN.com Inc. located at 5901 W. Century Blvd., 9th Floor, Los Angeles, CA  90045-5421.

### General

TollFreeForwarding.com respects the privacy of every individual who visits our website and responds to our interactive advertisements or sends us email. This Privacy Policy statement outlines the information TollFreeForwarding.com will collect and how we will use that information. This Privacy Policy statement will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared when you visit TollFreeForwarding.com, respond to our web-based advertisements or send us email.

### Security

All online order forms from TollFreeForwarding.com utilize a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol to provide "secure sessions" for our visitors. Through the "secure session," information that you input into a TollFreeForwarding.com online order form will be sent and will arrive privately and unaltered at a TollFreeForwarding.com server. This security prohibits other companies and web users from being able to access your information. 

### Personally-identifiable Information

TollFreeForwarding.com will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (that is, your name, address, telephone number, or email address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily.  

TollFreeForwarding.com obtains information about individuals in these main ways: 

  * When you visit this website or contact us directly about becoming a customer or obtaining other information
  * When you become a TollFreeForwarding.com customer,
  * When individuals use a customer’s phone number (the service that we provide),
  * When a customer uses our service to download data about their account.
  * When you are a service provider to TollFreeForwarding.com, and
  * Through the normal TollFreeForwarding.com employment process.

Our Data Processing Amendment governs our processing of any information obtained as a result of the customer or service provider relationship. You can read our commitment to customers and service providers, and our fair information practices in the Data Processing Amendment.

### Information that we collect

TollFreeForwarding.com will collect personal information that you submit to us. 

  * From our customers, we collect account information. This includes personal name, email address, business name, and credit card or other payment information.
  * We collect call detail records (CDR) on behalf of our customers. This data includes the phone number dialed, the person who is calling and the time of day and duration of the call. If the customer has selected the service, we provide call audio recordings stored for the duration that the customer selects. This information is only available to the customer and TollFreeForwarding.com customer support employees through a secured portion of the website. We do not share, sell, or otherwise distribute this data. This data is not used for any marketing activities. This data is retained for the duration of the customer account.
  * When diagnosing call quality problems, we record calls for use by our employees to work on support tickets and troubleshoot issues. These recordings are stored for the duration of the troubleshooting period and are automatically deleted afterwards. They are not available outside the company and all employees accessing these recordings to troubleshoot issues are audited for each access.
  * We collect non-personally-identifiable information, as listed below.

The following are some examples of when TollFreeForwarding.com may require that you provide personally-identifiable information: 

  * to complete an online order for a product or service
  * to enter an online contest or sweepstakes
  * to sign up for our newsletter or other advertisements
  * to request more information about new or current TollFreeForwarding.com products or services 

If you have already submitted this information and would like for us to remove it from our records, please contact us at [Support@TollFreeForwarding.com](mailto:Support@TollFreeForwarding.com). We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our existing files. All TollFreeForwarding.com customers are able to review and correct any personally-identifiable information we have collected by logging into their Online Control Center, which is accessed by clicking "Login" at the top right of the TollFreeForwarding.com homepage. 

When you do provide us with personally-identifiable information, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise:

  * we may store and process that information to better understand all customer needs and how we can improve our products and services for all customers
  * we may use that information to contact you with new promotions and announcements if you have previously provided your permission
  * we may use this information to refine and customize your experience on TollFreeForwarding.com
  * we may contact you if we have questions about your account

TollFreeForwarding.com will not sell personally-identifiable information to third parties. We may share information with business partners. We are committed to giving you the choice whether or not we use your information for marketing purposes or share information with business partners.

### Non-personally-identifiable Information Collected Automatically

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website and/or Internet Service Provider from which you linked to our site or advertisement.

Similar to personally-identifiable information, we will not sell non-personally-identifiable information to third parties. We may share non-personally identifiable information with business partners.

### Use of Cookies

When you view one of our websites or advertisements, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and will be used to determine ways to improve our websites, advertisements, products or services. For example, cookies allow us to tailor a website to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

### Laws and Legal Rights

We may disclose your information (including personal information) if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with an applicable statute, regulation, rule or law, a subpoena, a search warrant, a court or regulatory order, or other valid legal process. We may disclose personal information in special circumstances when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the TollFreeForwarding.com Terms of Service, to detect fraud, or to protect the safety and/or security of our users, the TollFreeForwarding.com website, or the general public. 

We also may be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

### GDPR

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), is a European privacy law approved by the European Commission in 2016 and will go into effect May 25th 2018. The GDPR will replace a prior European Union privacy directive known as Directive 95/46/EC which has been the basis of European data protection law since 1995. The GDPR is an attempt to strengthen, and modernize EU data protection law and enhance individual rights and freedoms, consistent with the European understanding of privacy as a fundamental human right. The GDPR regulates, among other things, how individuals and organizations may obtain, use, store, and remove personal data. In a nutshell, it's giving EU citizens and residents control over their personal data while simplifying the regulatory environment for international business that takes place in the EU.

The Data Protection Principles include requirements such as: 

  * Personal data collected must be processed in a fair, legal, and transparent way and should only be used in a way that a person would reasonably expect. 
  * Personal data should only be collected to fulfill a specific purpose and it should only be used for that purpose. Organizations must specify why they need the personal data when they collect it. 
  * Personal data should be held no longer than necessary to fulfill its purpose. 
  * People covered by the GDPR have the right to access their own personal data. They can also request a copy of their data, and that their data be updated, deleted, restricted, or moved to another organization. 

We are committed to adhering to GDPR rules for all of our EU customers

### Data Processing Addendum

We offer a data processing addendum (DPA) for our customers who collect data from folks in the EU. Our DPA offers contractual terms that meet GDPR requirements and that reflect our data privacy and security commitments to our customers. There is no new action needed on the part of our current TollFreeForwarding.com customers.

### Personnel Matters

If you are a TollFreeForwarding.com employee or applicant, we collect information you voluntarily provide to us. We use the information collected for Human Resources purposes in order to administer benefits to workers and screen applicants.

You may contact us in order to (1) update or correct your information, (2) change your preferences with respect to communications and other information you receive from us, or (3) receive a record of the information we have relating to you. Such updates, corrections, changes and deletions will have no effect on other information that we maintain, or information that we have provided to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy prior to such update, correction, change or deletion.

### Use of service by minors

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. The TollFreeForwarding.com Service is not designed for or directed to children under the age of 16. We do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 16.

### Policy Application

By using the TollFreeForwarding.com website or contacting us directly, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you should not engage with our website, or use our services. Continued use of the website, direct engagement with us, or following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy that do not significantly affect the use or disclosure of your personal information will mean that you accept those changes. 

### Declining Email Offers

As outlined in this Privacy Policy statement, we will only send email promotions or announcements to you if you have previously provided your permission for us to do so. Although many customers tell us they appreciate receiving notice of these carefully designed promotions and announcements, we recognize the importance of providing you with choices. At any time, you may unsubscribe from our email list by filling out a simple online unsubscribe form. All email offers that you receive from TollFreeForwarding.com will inform you of how to decline receiving further email offers.

### Who to Contact

If you have submitted personally-identifiable information through TollFreeForwarding.com or interactive advertisement, and would like that information deleted from our records, please contact us at our email address, [Support@TollFreeForwarding.com](mailto:Support@TollFreeForwarding.com). We will use our best efforts to delete this information from our existing files.
